{
    "id": "52aef8675fd34d86aaec1ddb75647c4e",
    "title": "How to join two sentences by using an infinitive",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "5dbddefd660f48e797d3e72b7e07d7da",
            "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I have engaged a private tutor ................................. me English.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to teach",
                        "for teaching"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The woman was .................................. mean to be popular.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "too"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I looked out of the window .................................... the green pastures.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for seeing",
                        "to see"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The proposal is ...................................... unreasonable to be accepted.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "so",
                        "very"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Our country expects every man ................................. his duty.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to do",
                        "doing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "My mother was very much delighted ................................... about my fatherâ€™s safe arrival.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to hear",
                        "to hearing",
                        "hearing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He works hard ........................................ the first rank.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to win",
                        "for winning"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He went to the USA ........................................ higher education.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to pursue",
                        "for pursuing",
                        "to pursuing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is .................................... weak to walk without help.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "too",
                        "very"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The tea is ..................................... hot for me to drink.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "so",
                        "very"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}